<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
   "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd" []>
<chapter id="getting_started">
    <title>Getting Started with Seam Scheduling</title>
    <para>
        This document describes all necessary actions and configurations
        that should be done for use Seam Scheduling in a web appplication.
        The description relies on a simple JSF application creation process from downloading
        the libraries to running the application in a browser.
        The process of application creation described here is common and does not depend on used IDE.
    </para>

    <section id="getting_started.downloading">
        <title>Downloading Seam Scheduling</title>

        <para>
            The latest release of CDI Schedule is available for download in Downloads area [@TODO: insert link to download].
            Binary files (uploaded there in *.bin.zip or *.bin.tar.gz archives) contains compiled, ready-to-use version of Seam Scheduling.
        </para>
        <para>
            To start with Seam Scheduling in computer file system, create a new folder with name "Seam Scheduling", 
            download and unzip the archive with binaries there.
            If you are using Maven, see Chapter 1. Installation [@TODO: insert link to chapter] to see how to use Seam Scheduling using Maven.
        </para>
        <para>
            For those who want to download and compile the Seam Scheduling by themselfs
            there is an article at JBoss community that describes the Seam Scheduling
            repository's structure overview and some aspects of working with it. [@TODO: insert link]
        </para>
    </section>

    <section id="getting_started.demo">
        <title>Simple JSF/Seam Application with Scheduling</title>

        <para>
            "Seam Scheduling Demo" — the simple application — is a simple application created to demonstrate Seam Scheduling features.
        </para>
        <para>
            If you are starting with Seam / Weld you can read Weld documentation here: http://docs.jboss.org/weld/reference/1.0.1-Final/en-US/html/
        </para>
    </section>
</chapter>